<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mediator :: Juice's documentation</title><link>https://juice-docs.creatorflow.io/core/mediator/index.html</link><description>MediatR provides three in-process messaging patterns. In Juice v9 all three can extend MessageBase so every message carries MessageId, CreatedAt, and TenantId automatically.
Pattern Interface Handler interface Use when Request/Response IRequest&lt;TResponse> IRequestHandler&lt;T, TResponse> Command or query — exactly one handler, returns a result Notification INotification INotificationHandler&lt;T> In-process fan-out — multiple handlers, no return value Stream Request IStreamRequest&lt;TResponse> IStreamRequestHandler&lt;T, TResponse> Async streaming — handler yields items one at a time NuGet Package Package Purpose MediatR Core MediatR library Juice.MediatR.Behaviors IdempotencyRequestBehavior&lt;,>, TransactionBehavior&lt;,,> Juice.MediatR.Contracts IIdempotentRequest interface Request / Response — Commands and Queries A request routes to exactly one handler and always returns a result. Use it for commands (state-changing operations) and queries (read-only operations).</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 20:23:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juice-docs.creatorflow.io/core/mediator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MediatR (v8.5.0)</title><link>https://juice-docs.creatorflow.io/core/mediator/v8.5.0/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 20:23:50 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://juice-docs.creatorflow.io/core/mediator/v8.5.0/index.html</guid><description>⚠ Archived — v8.5.0 This page describes the pre-v9 Juice API. For current documentation see Messaging.
We provide IdentifiedCommand pattern to deduplicate incoming events with built-in EF backend (SqlServer/PostgreSQL) or Redis backend. Please follow the link Implement idempotent Commands for more information.
await mediator.Send(new IdentifiedCommand&lt;OriginCommand>(originCommand, originCommandId));The request manager will verify originCommandId does not exist before sending originCommand to your OriginCommandHandler.
EF backend Please register request management services with your application schema before use.</description></item></channel></rss>